<news>
<time>2017-09-14-01-09-35-030</time>
<eugene>
<headline>Alleged shooter of OSP trooper in Creswell identified | Local ... - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>Eugene police seek man, 24, in connection with burglaries - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>University of Oregon athlete's wrongful-death trial begins | Local ... - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>Bicyclist injured in Eugene crash Tuesday night - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>Eugene Concert Orchestra seeks personnel manager - The Register-Guard</headline>
</eugene>
<us>
<headline>What would China do if North Korea and the United States go to war? - South China Morning Post</headline>
<headline>President Donald J. Trump Proclaims September 15, 2017, as National POW/MIA Recognition Day - The White House (blog)</headline>
<headline>President Donald J. Trump Proclaims September 15 through October 15, 2017, as National Hispanic Heritage Month - The White House (blog)</headline>
<headline>WEISS: America's abdication from the fight for global security - University of Virginia The Cavalier Daily</headline>
<headline>Medicare for All or State Control: Health Care Plans Go to Extremes - New York Times</headline>
</us>
<world>
<headline>World's oldest captive panda Basi dies in China - BBC News</headline>
<headline>How much does the iPhone X cost around the world? - Telegraph.co.uk</headline>
<headline>Myanmar's Nobel Peace laureate is hiding from the world as her country moves closer to genocide - Vox</headline>
<headline>Russia World Cup travel guide: How can I get the best tickets? And what to do when I am there? - The Independent</headline>
<headline>New 'real world' diesel tests fail to prevent rush hour pollution peak - The Guardian</headline>
</world>
</news>
<message type="test">
<time>2017-09-14-01-09-40-024</time>
<word>dying</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-01-45-57-820</time>
<word>men</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-02-34-07-661</time>
<word>hip</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-02-41-35-280</time>
<word>plotted</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-03-03-19-738</time>
<word>head</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-03-38-04-580</time>
<word>male</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-03-47-38-947</time>
<word>prisoner</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-05-21-42-736</time>
<word>side-by-side</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-05-22-23-080</time>
<word>money-maker</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-05-32-05-990</time>
<word>wife</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-09-14-05-39-33-487</time>
<word>bed</word>
</message>
