<news>
<time>2017-10-11-00-11-48-124</time>
<eugene>
<headline>Mother, toddler found man hanging in park - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>Eugene man charged with attacking father and police - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>South Eugene homeless camp poised for expansion - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>Public forums set on recruiting new Eugene police chief - The Register-Guard</headline>
<headline>Forums begin in hiring of Eugene police chief - The Register-Guard</headline>
</eugene>
<us>
<headline>Dairy-based and Soy-based Desserts Market in the United States of ... - MarketWatch</headline>
<headline>Joint Statement between the United States of America and the ... - The White House (blog)</headline>
<headline>Diverse United States divided on symbols of patriotism - USA TODAY</headline>
<headline>How Russia Harvested American Rage to Reshape US Politics - New York Times</headline>
<headline>Erdogan is bullying America. Trump should do something. - Washington Post</headline>
</us>
<world>
<headline>How Israel Caught Russian Hackers Scouring the World for US Secrets - New York Times</headline>
<headline>The Netherlands Is In A World Of Trouble, And Argentina Might Be Too - FiveThirtyEight</headline>
<headline>Messi lifts Argentina into World Cup with Uruguay, Colombia; Chile out - ESPN FC</headline>
<headline>China poised to replace US as leading donor to developing world: report - CNN</headline>
<headline>Green Squash Deemed World's Biggest Brings Triple Win To RI Grower - NPR</headline>
</world>
</news>
<message type="test">
<time>2017-10-11-00-11-54-015</time>
<word>insane</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-00-20-42-715</time>
<word>sleepers</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-00-50-20-268</time>
<word>sacred-idiots</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-00-57-30-501</time>
<word>wrapt</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-01-09-09-894</time>
<word>solemn</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-01-22-26-117</time>
<word>stoping</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-01-23-51-496</time>
<word>stepping</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-01-33-14-092</time>
<word>quiet</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-02-13-49-686</time>
<word>sisters</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-02-44-10-433</time>
<word>stepping</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-02-45-56-746</time>
<word>quiet</word>
</message>
<message type="auto">
<time>2017-10-11-03-15-43-496</time>
<word>pausing</word>
</message>
